Process Server/Executive

ROBERT SMITH

Phone: (123) 456 78 99
Email: info@qwikresume.com
Website: www.qwikresume.com
LinkedIn: linkedin.com/qwikresume
Address: 1737 Marshville Road,

Alabama

Objective

Accomplished and dynamic professional committed to pursuing a career into a management position, with solid and diverse experience in a variety of fields managing overall operations and optimizing organizational processes. Highly motivated, dependable, and demonstrates professionalism in organizational goals while displaying effective multi-tasking and time management skills.

Skills

Manager, Law Enforcement, Typing 50 Wpm, Communication Skills, Team Building, Team Leadership, Teamwork.

Work Experience

Process Server/Executive

ABC Corporation - February 2007 - November 2007

- Handled serving of court orders and processes, such as summonses and subpoenas.
- Received papers to be served from the magistrate, court clerk, or attorney.
- · Handled court filings for civil and criminal cases and conducted court research and copy work.
- Handled delivery of Court Legal Papers and deposition subpoenas all over the San Francisco Bay Area.
- Performed court case monitoring and handled tax filing.
- Reviewed the documents to be served to verify they are completely filled out, signed and have accurate contact information.
- Serve papers including, but not limited to, subpoenas and summons and complaints to offices and homes.

Process Server/Executive

ABC Corporation - 2003 – 2007

- served civial papers for the courts Cass, Jackson counties Jackson County Detention Center.
- CORRECTIONS OFFICER.
- provided safety and security to inmates in a firm fair and consistant manor 2008-2009 assited cert team in emergency cituations.
- fights assisted in teaching cpr aed to fellow guards completed 120 academy with jackson county processing reports and helping as acting sgt.
- while sgt.
- · was not on floor.
- ASSISTED IN TRAINING NEW CORRECTIONS OFFICER WITH IN MY FIRST WEEK AT THE JAIL worked with protective custody inmates and high risk inmates (prison returns).

Education

Diploma